Hi! My name is

Francisco A. Sarría. I'm Front-end Developer pasionated for react.js/next.js

Currently pleased developing with React.js and Next.js and fascinated with all the JAMStack ecosystem.

About me

I am from Córdoba, Argentina and started building webs with html, css and php (just a little bit) back in 2011.

In 2012 start working with Drupal 7 for several years but never happy with it.

In 2018 I left the web world and in 2019 started with Wordpress. In late 2019 I discovered the big javascript world: React.js, Vue.js, Angular, etc. and start studying development in Platzi (and in another webs and youtube) focus to get into the React.js world.



Personal info

40 years old

Single, without children

Córdoba city, Argentina

Advanced English

Contact info

+54 351 156193912

franasarria@gmail.com

linkedin: /francisco-andres-sarria

www.fransarria.ml

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), HTML, CSS/Sass

Libraries & Frameworks

React.js, Next.js

Tools & Platforms

Git, Vercel, Netlify, Wordpress

Design

Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator

A little experience with:

Node.js, Express, Contentful, GraphQL/ApolloGraphQL, TypeScript, Firebase, Netlify, jQuery.

Experience

2020 - Present: Freelance

Developing with React.js and Next.js commercial and personal projects.

2019 - Present: "Persuasiva"

Communication agency.

Role: Web designer and developer, nessletter, motion graphics.

2018 - 2019: Law Buffet and Freelance

In the buffet I worked in the administration. As a freelancer I've worked with Wordpress.

2011 - 2018: Freelancing

Designing and building webs with plain HTML and CSS and Drupal 7.

Education

2019 - Present

Platz, educational online platform.

Profile: https://platzi.com/p/francisco-sarria/

2018

Udemy:

Javascript (ES6), HTML 5, CSS/SASS.

2017

"Introduction to User Experience Design" in Georgia Tech.

Google Analitycs and AdWords Certification.

2006 - 2010

"Multimedia Design" in a local institute called IES Siglo 21.

2006 - 2009

Photography technique in the province technical school.

2004

Took the T.OE.F.E.L. test after 7 years studying english.

Recent JAMStack projects

https://artyasc-panchitosarria.vercel.app/ *Under development*

https://fransarria.ml
Personal web

https://andresalvarez.com.ar/
Simple React.js/Next.js web for an accountant.

Some other works

http://capitalinas.com/

http://www.silviaoliva.com.ar/

http://www.proartecordoba.org/

http://www.nanzer.com.ar/

http://www.famigliarossi.com.ar/

http://zmsa.com.ar/